Okay. Amazing.
I mean, we have three minutes, but I'm going to let these guys
get started a little bit early since there's no seats left, so.
Damn. Dang. Impressive.
So this is Daniel Jones and Tomasz Maj.
These guys are going to be giving you very interesting case study.
But they're professionals.
As you can see from the not contrasting at all vibes here.
Absolute dream team.
So take it away guys.
Okay.
I'm surprised
people won't put off by the scary, like, AI enhanced face.
Yeah, it's heavily very good.
It was photoshopped a bit.
You know, I wish they put more hair on my head.
So. Right. I'll kick things off.
As you might have guessed.
The topic is about generating more software faster.
And we'll come back to that theme at the end.
And this is really the story of some work that we've done together.
One of us is an ex McKinsey consultant
and the other works at a small boutique consultancy.
I'm not sure if you can tell which one is which.
But yeah, so I'm Daniel Jones or
DJ to my friends because of the initials, not because of the raving.
I'm not actually a DJ or anything like that.
I'm Thomas. Thomas is Thomas.
What is your Polish?
You can tell you can use one of the five versions of my name if you want.
Yeah, but it's only for Polish people.
It's an internal secret we have. Yeah.
So I work for a small consultancy.
Boutique consultancy, I think is the most flattering way to put it, called re:cinq.
We're based in northern Europe and we do AI native transformation.
So we come from a background of cloud native transformation, helping people
with, you know, cloud, Kubernetes, all those kind of things.
And we're seeing the same kind of patterns around transformation.
And why
adopting agentic coding practices and getting the most out of AI
is not just as simple as like, give people some Claude Code licenses.
There are changes that need to happen around and alongside that.
So we'll go into a bit of that in this talk.
Yeah.
So yeah we'll talk about the background.
So I'll tell you a bit about Odevo.
So we're all on the same page.
Then we'll continue talking about the training.
And then together we'll wrap it up with some measurable impact
that we have had now in with this.
So yeah the background the background of it is
Odevo is a property residential property management company
that has both owns property managers and also provides them services.
Which one of those is technology, right.
And in the recent ranking we are the third
largest tech company, private tech company in Sweden.
So if you take loveable number one, there's another one in the middle.
We don't talk about them. And then it's us number three.
So that's just how relatable it is.
And yeah, we are global right?
We are the third largest.
And we have we offer the full suite.
So we own the full entire value chain of residential property management.
And property management in this context is like, you know, when renting a flat
and you've got to pay some company like £100 a month or whatever to like,
make sure the bins are in good order and the communal lighting
and the HVAC works and the lifts and the elevators and.
Many other things like that, the bills are accounted for and that nothing breaks.
Or if it breaks, it gets fixed.
And the UK, of course, now it's all the fire safety.
Or in the US it's elevator safety and all the others, everything around it
we own as the full suite of services
and to end in residential property management.
Yeah. And it's quite important stuff in that.
Like the kind of people that your end customers, your end users like they
some of them are volunteers.
So having good software that works well makes their life a lot easier.
They're often under kind of equipped for the job.
They have to manage finances and maybe they're volunteers.
So if Odevo can do things really well, then there's a large scope
to make lots of people's lives better and improve their living circumstances.
Yeah, yeah. So we're growing like crazy.
We've been acquiring a new company pretty much every week.
We have to take into account an M&A, in our case, is taking a company
that's usually a father, a mother, a kid and a dog that are a property manager.
And we sort of we buy this at scale across the across the northern hemisphere,
from the US to, to, to Europe and everywhere else.
So we're present in the United States, Mexico, United Kingdom.
We originally started in Sweden.
And then we started growing, expanding towards the UK,
United States and and the rest of the world.
And we're right now focusing in which we can't grow more time zones.
It's becoming a bit problematic.
So we're sticking to the ones we have and probably will continue growing either
probably north
in some parts, south and others, or trying to bring everything together.
So yeah, it's a massive, massive change.
Seven and seven years, we've gone from 50,000
homes under management to two, 2.5 million
from 1000 employees to 14,000 employees.
And we continue growing and continue expanding.
What? Yeah, as a company.
And those all of those acquisitions and having different solutions
in different places means that there's a really heterogeneous tech
kind of situation.
So a number of different tech stacks you have, like.
If you have a tech stack, you think you have a tech stack,
we probably have it.
So we have we have everything we have, we got we even have some,
some sort of we use software that's completely there's no UI to it.
And you call a server
and it takes sometimes like 30 minutes to just upload information about it's
it's also very outdated heavily paper and pen and paper industry.
So in the UK we still have a property manager will put
how much he has to charge a homeowner association, how much money on to post it.
And those posters tend to be lost sometimes.
So stuff like that happens still today, which is really cool
that the power of digitization in property management is massive.
It's everything.
There's just there's a win and there's a case for all sorts of things,
which will be very important when we talk about the impact of this training.
But yeah. Yeah. And so there's lots of different tech stacks.
And because of the acquisitions there's also a lot of different cultures.
There's a lot of different processes, a lot of different methodologies.
So when we're talking about, you know, it wasn't so much
that there's like one way of doing things and that's what needed to be evolved.
There were loads of different ways of doing things.
Which brings us on to like the AI situation when we started this journey.
When we when I joined in 2024.
So we had some things in place.
We we've been already using GitHub
Copilot in our, our developers were using GitHub Copilot.
We've built our own chat solution
based on on OpenAI's API, which is a dogfight for.
The main reason for
that was that we process a lot of sensitive data, customer data.
We did not want to sort of have our employees go wild and upload
the information that shouldn't be uploaded to different types of chats.
So we build our own solution.
And somewhere we were having a bit of Claude islands,
we would say like there would be 1 or 2 devs who got very excited, decided
to get a license on their own and use Claude
or other tools, but it was just sort of like an island here.
One guy there, one guy there, nothing serious.
And we weren't really there wasn't
really a adoption of a massive adoption of AI in the devs job.
Right?
So we only had around 30% and it was most GitHub copilot.
When we talk about time to merge, things took a lot of time when it came to PR
sizes, usually big once a week, sometimes more, even less often.
And of course the devs were not.
It was quite slow, so we did invest a lot of time
when I joined in 2024 to systemize a way of working around
flow, around maximizing and sort of the the speed and making it transparent
because most teams did not even know they were underperforming.
They just everything was kumbaya.
Everyone was like, hey, let's go.
We created that transparency, which then helped in adopting
AI and the trainings, making them more successful.
Right. We had to create that, that knowledge.
And that was something that really made the future journey much easier,
because we already spent a year and a half bringing modern ways of working
to the teams across all these tech stacks, all these cultures.
So that was that was an important investment in the beginning.
But yeah, we were okay.
But it wasn't really like a massive.
So a nice spoiler alert.
Yeah disruption is coming.
And we we already knew that AI is going to be a big deal.
Like this was still pre summer 2025.
We again had more and more of these islands Claude islands popping up.
And it's nice that Claude island
that would be a nice place or a scary place for some maybe.
But we saw that there was more and more talk about it, and we realized
we had to partner up with someone to help us in this journey.
To help all the devs,
we made a very bold statement that we're going to train
every single developer and organization on the same way around AI,
so we we create an RFP with AI,
those I mean, all the we we sent it out.
I made a big mistake of putting on LinkedIn.
I am looking for an AI training company.
I got a lot of 15 year olds telling me they have 25 years of experience
doing AI training. That was weird.
Or of course, I had several people who told me there had been
they've been doing agentic before agent was a thing, so
I got around 80 submissions or people reach out to me.
I had to sort of simmer down and tell them to relax.
We then we got ten that we really looked for, looked good.
We ran several talks with them
and we landed with.
An idiot with a mustache.
That's exactly what we called him.
Where he couldn't remember his name.
What's his name? Oh, it's the guy with the mustache.
Yes, yes. Wearing ridiculous clothes as well.
So that was summer last year.
And, I mean, it seems like ancient history,
but that was like before, you know, Opus 4.5.
It was before spectrum development was kind of becoming popular.
It was like September when I think spec Kit came out.
So you folks were quite ahead of the curve and seeing that this wave was coming.
And we really wanted we really our main takeaway
was with AI, bad things get worse and good things can get better.
So we really wanted to have someone who could help us in that journey.
Yeah, it wasn't easy, right?
We really did land with three companies in the end that were very close.
But again, the mustache. Exactly. Was the most.
You want to win more business, get good facial hair.
That's one option anyway.
So let's talk about training.
I probably should have given some kind of like photosensitive sensitive
epilepsy warning.
So if anyone is like sensitive to flashing lights
or you've got a stinking hangover, definitely not me.
You might not want to look at the brightly colored slides.
So I'm going to talk to you now about the training, how we did it,
and some of the things we did before the training to make it more successful.
This is not as a sales pitch.
This is so that you can go and do this inside your organizations
and think about the kind of fundamentals that need to be in place to do this.
Well. So the first thing
told you it
first thing that we did is a process called discovery.
So for folks who aren't consultants, this is where you go into an organization
and you figure out what's the current lay of the land.
And this is a really important thing to do because of this very authentic
Dora report quote might be.
But in the 2025 Dora report, there were a couple.
There was one that was, I think, August ish.
It made the point, after looking at a couple of thousand companies
that if you are not doing software development well at the moment and you
throw agentic coding at the problem, things are going to get worse.
You're optimizing a system, you're making one part
of an interconnected system go really fast.
You will expose bottlenecks elsewhere.
If you're doing software delivery well and you start adopting agentic coding,
then things will go much faster
and you'll be on a hockey stick of like exponential performance.
The tricky part is that nobody knows where this balance point is.
Like how crap do you have to be?
Is it that how bad software development do you have to be to go slower?
Like, are you in a good place or not?
And as an industry, we haven't quite figured that out, but the kind of things
that we needed to look at across the various different teams and cultures
at Odevo were things like CI/CD, do you have a platform?
This is a current bugbear of mine with
I shouldn't tell too many tangents about other customers,
but if you don't have a platform
like you can't ship code reliably and quickly, and then you're just
going to generate all this code and have no where to go with it.
Do you have tests?
If agents can't run tests to find out they've broken your software,
don't be surprised when they break your software.
If you're you don't have coding standards.
If you're the humans in your organization, don't agree what good looks like,
then there's a very low chance that an agent is going to be able
to produce code that your team is going to approve of.
So there are lots of things that are worth looking at.
And the optimist in me likes to think
that maybe this is another opportunity as an industry, that we get to
look at those fundamentals and go, look, we really need to improve these.
And we really wanted we made it very clear in the RFP
that we do expect to discover recession that we will pay for because we're
I mean, it's very easy to make assumptions without understanding.
So we really wanted our partner to get to know our company better.
We've had some bad experiences when companies came in
with all these assumptions which were not right.
So we really wanted the the partner.
We're partnering with this guy to get to know the people
that will do the training for it, to know the company.
This was a very important part of making this a success, I think.
So, yeah.
If you're going on an coding journey in your organization,
make sure that you're bringing attention to these fundamentals and like
raising the flag if if they're not, if they're not good enough.
The next thing that we did was workshops.
And we got lots of people
in the fancy office, which is Spotify's old office.
So it's quite cool to be be be there.
But doing things in person, both to
we did the initial set of training in person,
but also we did workshops to explore how people felt about all of this.
So hands up if anyone knows what liberating structures are.
Panels, you know you're just lazy.
Can't be bothered to hand up.
So Liberating Structures is like a menu of different meeting formats
and ways of facilitating conversations that tend to
subvert power dynamics and make sure that idiots with loud
voices like me don't dominate an entire conversation.
So we used a couple of these in person to ask people, you know,
what do you feel about the upcoming AI training that you're about to do?
What emotions do you experience? Are you are you scared?
Are you worried that your job satisfaction is going to go?
Are you worried about the not being motivated in future?
We also did a round of questions using a format called trees,
which apparently any Russian speakers in the room.
It's some acronym for the Creative Theory of Problem solving.
So we posed a question to the group, which was, imagine that you work
for a property management company called Odevo,
and they're about to hire 200 junior software developers
that come from a country and a culture where they always say yes.
They never say no.
They don't push back on anything and they never sleep.
They've got an intravenous drip of Red bull,
and they're just going to code all day and all night.
How could we make sure that this is a bigger disaster as possible?
And then we everybody contributed their ideas and chatted amongst themselves.
Next question was what do we do here?
That's a bit like some of those bad things.
And then you see everyone kind of looking at each other going,
can I say that the testing is not good enough?
Yeah, it was really cool.
That was also unanimous across all these different tech stacks.
There's cultures. They started saying, you do it.
We also do it.
It was like a lot of these like Spider-Man memes situation.
It was really everyone was like, oh my God, you don't test.
We don't either. Why? And then yeah, it was.
And this is
important in terms of reducing reactants, reducing people's
hesitancy, reducing the fear that they have.
Getting them
to start thinking about the solutions they're going to
need to make this work better.
So this is if you take anything away from all of this, really get people on board
and getting speaking to each other face to face, empathizing with each other,
find out what their fears are so
then you can have a more sensible conversation with them in the future.
And we also did a
we did a pilot version of the training as well, to learn
all the to get all the little things that could not go right in the big session.
So we did a pilot version that was on November 11th, a very important date.
It's Polish Independence Day.
So please remember 1111 is pushing dependance.
And we did a pilot. And that also helped, right?
Because we we did in a small group, we realized all the things
that could go bad or right or whatever, what to watch out for.
And that made it.
Then the big one where we had 80 people much more successful, I think.
Cool.
Yeah, I learned lots of important things about Poland when working with Tomasz,
one of which is don't go out drinking with a tall Polish person
the night before, delivering training or delivering a conference talk.
The Jagermeister last night might have been slightly surplus to requirements.
Anyway, we're already kind of 15 minutes
in, so we probably need to speed up something about training technique.
If you end up going through training, delivering any of this yourself,
or trying to upskill your peers, a really powerful technique
is after just getting somebody to do an exercise is, what did we just do?
So we would deliver a training module, get into an exercise of
and we talk about the syllabus in the moment.
But draw up live okay. What did we just do.
Okay. So you install Claude. Where did that come from. Okay.
You typed in a prompt where did that prompt go.
And then it called a tool. Okay.
Where do tools actually execute.
How does the model decide which tool to use.
And drawing this up piece by piece means that you can
leverage different types of mental machinery that we have.
So it's got social importance because people remember
sitting there awkwardly going,
oh, I've got to answer the question because they did it with asking.
We're not going to go on until we've answered.
People contribute things.
Funny things happen.
It's a visual way of representing stuff.
So it really cements people's knowledge
in a way that just doing the exercises doesn't.
So I would really recommend trying to use a technique like that when you're a.
And make the workshop in person.
That was also a massive thing.
We really brought everyone into the office in person.
We fed them, of course we did give them, which is a big thing in Sweden.
We fed them.
We then had an after party,
everything around that, but by bringing them in into the office,
telling them the first half of the day, no laptops, you were going to talk it out.
That also made the training stick more right rather than than being,
of course, doing multitasking and not listening to the guy
with the mustache, putting them in the office
to see each other, to meet each other, to put a oh, this oh, you it's you.
Okay. That also made a massive change.
And we pushed for that heavily that it has to be in person.
It has to be in Stockholm. Cool.
So the syllabus then in terms of what we actually taught
people, really fundamental thing teaching people about context
context management and maximum effective context windows.
If you don't understand that, the more you add
into your context window, the more off the rails the LLM is going to get.
Then people start doing daft things, like adding every possible instruction
for every possible scenario into their agents.
MD, which has been shown in a couple of academic studies.
Now to have negative impacts, you're better off having no instructions
in your agents MD than lots of them.
For example, we also did exercises with old models
that are easy to get to hallucinate
and to do prompt biasing to demonstrate people the failure cases.
I shouldn't go in standards.
We don't
need to train people on how to use coding agents on the happy path.
It's when it goes wrong.
When they work, it's magic and you just get working code out at the end.
So the important part is teaching people about the failure modes.
And that's what the first module was all about.
There's a big jump between using something like VS code, GitHub Copilot,
and Claude Code.
For a lot of people psychologically, like when you're in VS code,
you choose which files are open and you can look at them any time you like.
When you're using Claude code in a terminal, then all of a sudden
the agent is doing stuff and it chooses what to show you.
For some people, that was quite a big jump.
So that's a thing to be aware of.
We talked to people about MCP and spectrum developments and eventually got onto
multi-agent workflows and things like Gastown, now Gas City,
which by doing all of those things, they then had the building blocks
by the end to think about how this would
be applied to a team process, not just to an individual.
Another thing that we did that was quite important
is we did not deliver this training all in one go.
So there's a journey that people need to go on.
And we did weekly half day modules and then at the end.
So okay, you've just learned about MCP.
Why don't you go away back to your desk, install the MCP,
ask it like can you figure out what ticket I should do next?
What do you think of the acceptance criteria?
And then allowing that to be pushed back and find out
whether this stuff works in real life, not just in a training exercise.
And make sure you tell IT ops that people will be installing
software on their laptops.
We lost like
15 to 30 minutes in our trainings because people couldn't install Docker.
That was great. Yes, win.
And another important part of this psychologically is people like
the training exercise is gave people a guided tour of like here's code,
here's how skills work.
But it's when they then go back to their own desks
and make their own minds up and get the chance to play with it
on their actual production code basis.
That's when people start to see the power of this kind of stuff,
rather than just when we're showing it to them.
So should we get to the impact?
So of course there's an impact.
Massive. Everything up, everything.
All the good things up, all the bad things down.
But yeah, but it really did.
We do see after now after we finished these trainings in February.
So we trained a whole entire group within.
Then I did a little more with others.
But in general by mid-February were finished with our core group of developers
and we are seeing a massive, massive we are seeing great things.
Right.
So in general, we're seeing AI adoption now at around 94% based on.
Did you use AI in your last ten years?
94% said at least in at least three or more,
50, 60% in ten out of ten, and then a bit less.
But only 6% of organizations did not use it.
And it's more interesting why rather than do it right.
So now we're doing interviews with that group on on this.
What's happening?
Why aren't you using it to make your life and a general
like what's what's blocking you?
We are seeing massive increase in time to market.
So we are able to push things faster.
We are able to build things smaller and better quality.
And of course yeah, it's it's also the the whole
merge and releasing things makes it much easier.
So we're seeing that.
And if you look at the PR throughput and it's constantly increasing right.
So it's it's transparent.
We've also built a series of dashboards.
And every dev can see every other dev's
where they are working, which repos they're working on.
We're making it super transparent and cross the org across all teams.
We've invested in that as well.
So we have this data on a click of a button.
You can even chat to it. You can have conversations.
So it's very easy to find what's working, what's not working.
And of course we're seeing a constant increase in it.
I think giving people tools we would probably see similar trends,
but I don't think they would be as impactful.
And that the training did it enabled that they're more intentional
how they use it and they use it, I think, in a much smarter way.
So people are not, you know, pumping everything onto Opus 4.7
just because they are they're experimental.
They're playing with things.
But, you know, all these metrics are great.
But I think the biggest impact of our AI transformation was in this,
this is this, you know, you can if you if you find enough
smart people in the room,
hopefully all of them will start, maybe not as exponential in our case
in this case, but there should be an increase.
Now the tools are getting better.
What we saw and if you go to the next slide was the boldness.
People are not afraid to try things.
And I think that's the biggest takeaway for me.
If anyone asks how do you measure a successful AI transformation?
It is how many more bold things are you doing?
How many experiments are you trying out?
Are you actually trying to do a full end to end agentic workflow?
So one of our we did a very bold move.
We took a platform that we've been building for eight years
wasn't a great success.
What we did is we took it and we rewrote it end to end rewrite.
It took us with the support of an external expert, but we rebuild it.
Feature parity 1 to 1 in three weeks.
So something that we've built for eight years, we were able to rewrite
in three weeks, feature parity 1 to 1.
And now we're continuing to build it,
have a team dedicated much smaller than we had before.
So that was 20 devs building it for eight years.
Now we have four devs building it with with AI.
That's that was a bold move trying to build a mobile app in three days.
We tried.
That didn't work out.
Yeah, not so great, but we tried.
So we're doing a lot of.
Also, if you remember when I showed you the map, right.
All that that fragmented software, all countries are doing different things.
It's also because of regulation of legal stuff, everything.
It's very complicated to build a single piece of software for all those markets.
But now we're trying we're going to try to build a dedicated platform
that will be able to tackle all the all the needs
of all the markets in a single source, in a single place,
and then, of course, customized with AI for their different needs.
But that could have
would have never happened last year or without this feeling of boldness.
We've got four minutes and 45 seconds and we've got quite a few slides.
So with this in particular.
So we did the coding training.
People were using Claude code on an individual basis.
One of the teams that Thomas mentioned took a step back
and was like, how do we reimagine our software delivery process?
Like working on individual stories just doesn't work
when you can go so quickly with coding agents.
So what they did was an entirely different approach.
That was AI.
First, they spent two weeks talking about product requirements,
speaking with their mouths, having everything
automatically transcribed, from which they then went on
to get agents to create a product requirements document.
And they really battle tested that.
They thought it through very deeply.
They sketched out the entity relationships or the business logic,
get that domain really well defined, then ship it off to agents to split
into like a task plan, kind of like spec-driven development,
but like upper level of abstraction, if you like.
And now developers pick up a couple of epics a day,
and if one developer wants to use be mad.
Sure, fine. If the one wants you spec it, fine.
Some people are still vibe coding, but they each have their own way of working.
Once they pick up an epic and they're no longer doing human code review.
So they will look at the code themselves.
They're not writing code anymore on that team, but they will do like 7
or 8 passes of a code review before then raising a PR,
which they will then self merge so they don't have the bottleneck of other
humans reading code, like humans doing static analysis of code is a silly idea
in the first place.
So they've gone fully
AI AI native in all of the steps,
and trying to use the existing scrum Kanban
methodologies is you're going to hit bottlenecks very, very quickly.
So once you've got those practices in place, then it's time
to reassess your SDLC and how you go about doing things.
And then and there's sharing this. Right.
So there again sharing we're making it more like we're using them
as a lighthouse.
Everyone can go and join, talk to them, see how they're doing.
So it's also a massive transformation.
Everybody's talking about sharing.
We've also talked about this. We do a podcast work.
Tomasz has been on it.
And so one of the developers on this team, so the latest episode
is all about this process and their methodology.
Speaking of which, the impact on people.
So this is the Dominic who's a would try to pronounce that last name.
It's a. How was it done authentically in.
A very nice Polish last name.
He doesn't speak Polish though, so he has a hard time.
Yeah, yeah.
So Dom, he was an AI skeptic when we came to the training.
He had previously got ChatGPT to write code in isolation, you know,
non-urgent and was like, this is rubbish.
It's never going to work.
And also had like quite legitimate ethical concerns about AI,
how the models of trained the energy usage and all of that kind of stuff.
It was when he had the opportunity to play with opus
45 back in November, and the freedom to explore that.
That's when he realized
that the previous beliefs weren't true and that when running a gently,
these tools can create good code that he would be proud of.
You will find in a lot of organizations people that trade vs code GitHub copilot
like a year ago and it was rubbish and they're like oh,
I think is never going to work. I tried it once.
It was crap. And it's never, ever going to be good.
You will find people like that and they need the opportunity to see
the current state of the art in order to change their minds.
And like Dom on the podcast was saying,
I haven't written any code at work for 4 or 5 months.
What was interesting is he's doing it for fun at home.
You know, just like
you might buy furniture from Ikea, but then do carpentry in your spare time.
That's what the craft has turned into for him.
Then we have Daniel, which is part of our dev team.
We have a dedicated team that focuses on developer experience.
He's also hasn't written code, and he's building all the tools
to improve the developer experience in our organization.
So they build like massive amount of tracking
and telemetry and observational tools and doing that all without writing code.
And he was one of the more one of our, like, top skill top performers,
I think, he said he's increased his performance by 2000 30s.
And then the final, the final colleague that I want to mention is Nicholas.
We invested in a trained trainer program from the start.
We made it very clear we want to have build this capability to train on AI
and then develop our training continuously, evolve it internally.
So Nicholas became a trainer.
He was also a high performer, already heavily doing things with.
He was also been educating on, like Ralph Wiggum loops and all that.
He's always been a heavy user of AI by becoming a trainer.
Trainer now goes to our to the remaining sort of companies
where we still have developers that weren't part of the initial one,
and training them, telling him about his experience.
And that makes it much more real.
I mean, mustache and tracksuit and all.
Yes, but if it's a real person that understands the industry
and can share their own real experience for working at Odevo,
that makes it even realer, right?
That makes it more people.
Some people don't like to be taught by others.
We have to end. No, but we do need to hurry up.
So the. Future.
And the way that we.
See the future, we have now shifted, I know I we shifted.
We realized that my investing in our engineers,
we've forgotten about another very important part of the organization,
which is our product colleagues, designers, Vas, product managers.
So now we're taking we've taken the train that worked very well for engineers.
And we shifted towards we've adjusted it.
We've pivoted a bit for our product colleagues.
And you will find that the product folks become the next bottleneck.
We've seen that in lots of different places.
Also seeing that massively in this, the Dominic has,
I think you mentioned in the podcast.
So this is and then the next step is once we turn our product managers,
we want to now train an AI and how to use basic things with Claude Code
and others to our remaining employees, which is pretty interesting.
It's 13,000 people that will need to educate on basic
use of AI, and we're seeing people are already using it.
We have financial managers or or accountants
using Claude Code to build local small apps for themselves.
So we want to help them.
We want to structure that with training as well.
Got three more slides so you and you will get lunch soon.
And then. Yeah.
And one thing we've also noticed and I hear more of that today.
I heard it like we are having some of our engineers saying I can't turn it off.
I it's 6 p.m., 7 p.m.
sometimes 1 a.m.
I'm the dopamine rush is real.
So now we're also having sort of discussions with like, hey, put it away.
Like yeah, go enjoy life, go outside.
I mean, in Sweden it's. A lot of cell.
You go outside.
I would love to tell you about Skinner boxes and the
psychology behind it, but it's a real the compulsion is a real thing.
Also, this hasn't happened in Endeavor's case, but Lauren Peat,
CEO of multitudes, did some research that showed that
in a lot of organizations, people are working overtime
because of the increased feature pressure of you've adopted agentic coding,
you should be doing loads more stuff, you should be getting lots more done,
and people are now actually doing overtime because of that perceived pressure.
Yeah.
So our goal and our ambition is to make everyone a builder.
We want to we want to pivot from software.
We build for our for our up coast to coast build software.
With our support. We're making that shift.
We really believe everyone at Odevo will be a builder, and we really want
14,000 people to be building stuff for themselves.
And in the past, like in the 70s, if you wanted a new business
process, right, you've got some paper, you made a form, you told people about it.
That's how you changed the business.
Then our software developers got involved.
And to leverage the power of computing,
like we had to devolve all of that to engineers
and then you couldn't make any changes yourself.
And this got worse in the cloud
era when everything was distributed and complex.
Now we can re-impose business users to solve their own problems,
like some of the product managers are using Claude Code now.
We're vibe coding and lovable
and other tools as well, and building things that are used every day.
So what we see is not that software development is going to go away.
Not that we're going to end up with software developers
needing to be made redundant
because of those bigger, bolder changes that people are now empowered to make.
We see a world of more software that is more bespoke, more usable,
solving individual people's
business problems rather than kind of big, slow software that takes years to.
Develop those complicated Excel models.
They used to be on someone else's hard drive.
We're moving that to vibe coded solutions that are usable, used by actual users
and organization, which is super exciting, but also a bit scary.
So yeah, fun journey ahead of us. If you
do we do questions or have we run over that?
Yes. Sorry. Lunch.
There's a very stern shaking the head at the back.
If you can spot me, I might be hard to find than happy to talk afterwards.
There's our LinkedIn QR codes, but other than that, I'll shut up and say
thank you and we can go into more detail afterwards.
Thanks everyone.
Enjoy lunch. There's plenty of food. Don't worry.
Don't need to rush.